Register of the Commonwealth Club of California records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Study Sections File, 1908-1983 (Boxes 257-382)
  - Correspondence and other material
    - War Service Section [World War I], 1917-1919 (Box-folder 378: 15-19)
      - Food Production Committee, 1918 (Box-folder 378: 22)
      - Labor Conservation Committee, 1918 (Box-folder 379: 1-6)
      - Liberty Loan Committee, 1918-1919 (Box-folder 379: 7-8)
      - War Savings Stamp Committee, 1917-1918 (Box-folder 379: 9-16, Folder 380: 1-5)
    - War Service Committees [World War II], 1942 (Box-folder 380: 6-8)
      - Civilian Defense Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 380: 9-14)
      - Food Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 380: 15)
      - Members in Service Liaison Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 380: 16)
      - Raw Materials Committee, 1942 (Box-folder 380: 17-18)
    - Water Problems Section, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 381: 1-14)
    - Water Problems Section, 1977-1982 (Box-folder 382: 1-6)
    - Water Resources Section, 1930 (Box-folder 382: 7-9)
    - Welfare Problems Section, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 382: 10)
    - Western Hemisphere Section, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 382: 11-12)
- Program File, 1916-2006 (Boxes 382-605)
  Clippings, correspondence, prepared texts of speeches, and other material, arranged chronologically by year, then alphabetically thereunder by name of prospective/actual speaker or event.
  - 1916, T. D. Boardman (Box-folder 382: 13)
  - 1918, Earl of Dunmore (Box-folder 382: 14)
  - 1919-1926 (Box-folder 382: 15-21)
  - 1927-1928 (Box-folder 383: 1-14)
  - 1928 (Box-folder 384: 1-8)
  - 1931, Elwood Mead (Box-folder 384: 9)
  - 1932
    - Radio debates (Box-folder 384: 10)
    - A-F (Box-folder 384: 11-16)
    - G-R (Box-folder 385: 1-12)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box-folder 385: 13-14)
    - S-T (Box-folder 385: 15-16)
    - U-Z (Box-folder 386: 1-4)
  - 1933
    - A-L (Box-folder 386: 5-15)
    - M-Y (Box-folder 387: 1-11)
  - 1934
    - Radio debates (Box-folder 387: 12)
    - A-B (Box-folder 387: 13-14)
    - C-M (Box-folder 388: 1-12)
    - N-W (Box-folder 389: 1-9)
  - 1935
    - A-J (Box-folder 389: 10-18)
    - L-T (Box-folder 390: 1-8)
    - University debates (Box-folder 390: 9)
  - 1936
    - A-C (Box-folder 390: 10-12)
    - D-T (Box-folder 391: 1-16)
    - W-Y (Box-folder 392: 1-2)
  - 1937
    - A-N (Box-folder 392: 3-16)
    - O-Y (Box-folder 393: 1-6)
  - 1938
    - A-H (Box-folder 393: 7-13)
    - I-U (Box-folder 394: 1-9)
    - University Debates (Box-folder 394: 10-12)
    - V-Y (Box-folder 394: 13-14)
  - 1939
    - A-Q (Box-folder 395: 1-15)
    - R-Y (Box-folder 396: 1-6)
  - 1940
    - A-G (Box-folder 396: 7-13)
    - H-W (Box-folder 397: 1-13)
  - 1941
    - A-R (Box-folder 398: 1-15)
    - S-T (Box-folder 399: 1-2)
    - Town hall of the air (Box-folder 399: 3)
    - V-Y (Box-folder 399: 4-6)
  - 1942
    - A-L (Box-folder 399: 7-16)
    - M-Z (Box-folder 400: 1-11)
  - 1943
    - A-D (Box-folder 400: 12-15)
    - E-Z (Box-folder 401: 1-15)
  - 1944
    - B (Box-folder 401: 16)
    - C-T (Box-folder 402: 1-15)
    - W (Box-folder 403: 1)
  - 1945
    - General (Box-folder 403: 2)
    - A-P (Box-folder 403: 3-17)
    - R-Y (Box-folder 404: 1-5)
  - 1946
    - General (Box-folder 404: 6)
    - A-E (Box-folder 404: 7-11)
    - Ford, Henry (Box-folder 404: 12)
    - G-H (Box-folder 404: 13-14)
    - Hoover, Herbert (Box-folder 404: 15)
    - M-Y (Box-folder 405: 1-8)
  - 1947
    - General (Box-folder 405: 9-10)
    - A-G (Box-folder 405: 11-17)
    - H (Box-folder 406: 1)
    - Hoover, Herbert (Box-folder 406: 2)
    - I-Z (Box-folder 406: 3-16)
  - 1948
    - A-R (Box-folder 407: 1-13)
    - S-Z (Box-folder 408: 1-5)
  - 1949
    - General (Box-folder 408: 6)
    - A-L (Box-folder 408: 7-16)
    - M-W (Box-folder 409: 1-9)
  - 1950
    - A-E (Box-folder 409: 10-14)
    - F-W (Box-folder 410: 1-13)
  - 1951
    - B (Box-folder 410: 14)
    - C-M (Box-folder 411: 1-9)
    - McCarthy, Joseph (Box-folder 411: 10)
    - N (Box-folder 411: 11)
    - Nixon, Richard (Box-folder 411: 12)
    - O-P (Box-folder 411: 13-14)
    - R-W (Box-folder 412: 1-5)
  - 1952
    - A-H (Box-folder 412: 6-14)
    - H-W (Box-folder 413: 1-14)
  - 1953
    - A (Box-folder 413: 15)
    - Adenauer, Konrad (Box-folder 413: 16)
    - B-P (Box-folder 414: 1-14)
    - R-Y (Box-folder 415: 1-7)
  - 1954
    - A-C (Box-folder 415: 8-12)
    - D-S (Box-folder 416: 1-12)
    - S-Y (Box-folder 417: 1-5)
  - 1955
    - B-H (Box-folder 417: 6-13)
    - J-T (Box-folder 418: 1-11)
    - V-W (Box-folder 419: 1-2)
  - 1956
    - A-G (Box-folder 419: 3-10)
    - H-R (Box-folder 420: 1-10)
    - W-Y (Box-folder 421: 1-2)
  - 1957
    - A-E (Box-folder 421: 3-11)
    - F-O (Box-folder 422: 1-11)
    - P-W (Box-folder 423: 1-4)
  - 1958
    - A-B (Box-folder 423: 5-7)
    - Bowman, Karl (Box-folder 423: 8)
    - C-N (Box-folder 424: 1-12)
    - O-Z (Box-folder 425: 1-8)
  - 1959
    - A-E (Box-folder 425: 9-13)
    - F-K (Box-folder 426: 1-5)
    - Khrushchev, Nikita Sergeevich (Box-folder 426: 6-14)
    - L-W (Box-folder 427: 1-12)
    - Y-Z (Box-folder 428: 1)
  - 1960
    - A-H (Box-folder 428: 2-12)
    - J-S (Box-folder 429: 1-9)
    - S-Z (Box-folder 430: 1-3)
  - 1961
    - A-H (Box-folder 430: 4-12)
    - J-Y (Box-folder 431: 1-10)
    - W (Box-folder 432: 1-2)
  - 1962
    - A-H (Box-folder 432: 3-11)
    - J-R (Box-folder 433: 1-12)
    - S-W (Box-folder 434: 1-5)
  - 1963
    - B-C. (Box-folder 434: 6)
      General note
      See Box 455, folders 1-5
    - D (Box-folder 434: 7)
    - Folkers, Karl (Box-folder 434: 8)
    - G-K (Box-folder 434: 9-13)
    - K-M (Box-folder 435: 1-6)
    - Ngo Dinh Nhu (Box-folder 435: 7-8)
    - O-R (Box-folder 435: 9-11)
    - S-W (Box-folder 436: 1-6)
  - 1964
    - A-D (Box-folder 436: 7-11)
    - E-P (Box-folder 437: 1-11)
    - P-W (Box-folder 438: 1-11)
  - 1965
    - A-B (Box-folder 438: 12-13)
    - B-L (Box-folder 439: 1-11)
    - M-Y (Box-folder 440: 1-12)
  - 1966
    - B-H (Box-folder 441: 1-11)
    - K-R (Box-folder 442: 1-6)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 442: 7)
    - S (Box-folder 442: 8-9)
    - Stilwell, Joseph, Jr. (Box-folder 442: 10)
    - T (Box-folder 442: 11-12)
    - U-X (Box-folder 443: 1-3)
  - 1967
    - A-H (Box-folder 443: 4-12)
    - J-S (Box-folder 444: 1-10)
    - S-X (Box-folder 445: 1-10)
  - 1968
    - A (Box-folder 445: 11)
    - B-H (Box-folder 446: 1-10)
    - Humphrey, Hubert (Box-folder 446: 11-12)
    - J (Box-folder 446: 13)
    - K-P (Box-folder 447: 1-11)
    - R (Box-folder 448: 1)
    - Rusk, Dean (Box-folder 448: 2-4)
    - S-W (Box-folder 448: 5-7)
  - 1969
    - A-G (Box-folder 448: 8-12)
    - H-P (Box-folder 449: 1-11)
    - R-Y (Box-folder 450: 1-8)
  - 1970
    - A-B (Box-folder 450: 9-12)
    - C-L (Box-folder 451: 1-12)
    - M-N (Box-folder 452: 1-3)
    - Nguyen, Cao Ky (Box-folder 452: 4)
    - P (Box-folder 452: 5)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 452: 6)
    - S-W (Box-folder 452: 7-11)
  - 1971
    - A-C (Box-folder 452: 12-15)
    - C-L (Box-folder 453: 1-11)
    - M-R (Box-folder 454: 1-5)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 454: 6)
    - S-W (Box-folder 454: 7-11)
  - 1963
    - B-C (Box-folder 455: 1-5)
      See also box 434
  - 1972
    - General (Box-folder 455: 6)
    - B-F (Box-folder 455: 7-13)
    - G-M (Box-folder 456: 1-10)
    - N-Z (Box-folder 457: 1-9)
  - 1973
    - A-B (Box-folder 457: 10-12)
    - B (Box-folder 458: 1)
    - Bleiberg, Robert M. (Box-folder 458: 2)
    - Bundy, McGeorge (Box-folder 458: 3)
    - Butz, Earl L. (Box-folder 458: 4)
    - C-M (Box-folder 458: 5-14)
    - Mahoney, David (Box-folder 459: 1)
    - Mohn, Einar (Box-folder 459: 2)
    - R (Box-folder 459: 3-8)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 459: 9)
    - S (Box-folder 459: 10-12)
    - T-W (Box-folder 460: 1-3)
    - Walker, Daniel (Box-folder 460: 4)
    - Y-Z (Box-folder 460: 5)
  - 1974
    - A-F (Box-folder 460: 1-3)
    - F-M (Box-folder 461: 1-11)
    - M-W (Box-folder 462: 1-10)
    - W (Box-folder 463: 1-2)
  - 1975
    - A-F (Box-folder 463: 3-11)
    - G-M (Box-folder 464: 1-11)
    - M-W (Box-folder 465: 1-13)
    - W-Z (Box-folder 466: 1-3)
  - 1976
    - Bailar, Benjamin (Box-folder 466: 4)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box-folder 466: 5)
    - Brown, Robert (Box-folder 466: 6)
    - Bush, George H. W. (Box-folder 466: 7)
    - Business Week panel (Box-folder 466: 8)
    - Byington, John S. (Box-folder 466: 9)
    - Dole, Robert (Box-folder 466: 10)
    - Dumke, Glenn S. (Box-folder 466: 11)
    - Duplain, George W. (Box-folder 466: 12)
    - Eban, Abba (Box-folder 466: 13)
    - Field, Mervin D. (Box-folder 466: 14)
    - Flanagan, Edward (Box-folder 466: 15)
    - Gardner, Richard N. (Box-folder 466: 16)
    - Green, Marshall (Box-folder 466: 17)
    - Hahm, Pyong-choon (Box-folder 466: 18)
    - Hamilton, Robert M. (Box-folder 466: 19)
    - Hanley, John W. (Box-folder 467: 1)
    - Hayakawa, S. I. (Box-folder 467: 2)
    - Henning, John P. (Box-folder 467: 3)
    - Hills, Carla A. (Box-folder 467: 4)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 467: 5)
    - Hodgson, James D. (Box-folder 467: 6)
    - Hoffman, Martin B. (Box-folder 467: 7)
    - Hopp, Eugene S. (Box-folder 467: 8)
    - Inauguration of officers, annual holiday concert (Box-folder 467: 9)
    - Janeway, Eliot (Box-folder 467: 10)
    - Jones, Reginald H. (Box-folder 467: 11)
    - Kabbani, Sabah (Box-folder 467: 12)
    - Kemp, Jack F. (Box-folder 467: 13)
    - Kenna, Douglas E. (Box-folder 467: 14)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 467: 15-17)
    - Kleinman, David (Box-folder 467: 18)
    - Kopp, Quentin I. (Box-folder 467: 19)
    - Lundborg, Louis B. (Box-folder 468: 1)
    - Lurie, Robert A. (Box-folder 468: 2)
    - Lynn, James T. (Box-folder 468: 3)
    - Maretti, Robert and John W. Gofman (Box-folder 468: 4)
    - Moscone, George R. (Box-folder 468: 5)
    - Murphy, Reg (Box-folder 468: 6)
    - Owens, Jesse (Box-folder 468: 7)
    - Pahlavi, Ashraf, Princess (Box-folder 468: 8)
    - Parker, C. Wolcott II (Box-folder 468: 9)
    - Perry, Lowell W. (Box-folder 468: 10)
    - Reed, Thomas C. (Box-folder 468: 11)
    - Richardson, Elliot (Box-folder 468: 12)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson (Box-folder 468: 13)
    - Rossides, Zenon (Box-folder 468: 14)
    - Saxon, David (Box-folder 468: 15)
    - Sayegh, Fayez A. (Box-folder 468: 16)
    - Schober, Frank J. (Box-folder 468: 17)
    - Schorr, Daniel L. (Box-folder 468: 18)
    - Seidman, William L. (replacement speaker for Virginia Knauer) (Box-folder 468: 19)
    - Simon, William E. (Box-folder 468: 20)
    - Simonidis, Anastassios (Box-folder 468: 21)
    - Smith, Mary Louise (Box-folder 468: 22)
    - Sneider, Richard L. (Box-folder 469: 1)
    - Stilwell, Richard (Box-folder 469: 2)
    - Stone, Irving (Box-folder 469: 3)
    - Taylor, Robert B. (Box-folder 469: 4)
    - Towsey, Kenneth (Box-folder 469: 5)
    - Tunney, John V. (Box-folder 469: 6)
    - Turkmen, Ilter (Box-folder 469: 7)
    - Ullman, Al (Box-folder 469: 8)
    - Wallace, George (Box-folder 469: 9)
    - Warren, Jack Hamilton (Box-folder 469: 10)
    - Westmoreland, William C. (Box-folder 469: 11)
    - Weyand, Fred C. (Box-folder 469: 12)
    - White, Barbara M. (Box-folder 469: 13)
    - White, Theodore H. (Box-folder 469: 14)
    - Zahedi, Ardeshir (Box-folder 469: 15)
  - 1977
    - Abdel-Rahman, Hasan (Box-folder 469: 16)
    - Adefarasin, J. A., Justice (Box-folder 469: 17)
    - Aitken, Wylie (Box-folder 469: 18)
    - Alexander, Clifford (Box-folder 469: 19)
    - Amsterdam, Anthony (Box-folder 469: 20)
    - Bagge, Carl (Box-folder 470: 1)
    - Bagley, William T. (Box-folder 470: 2)
    - Barbagelata, John and George Moscone debate (Box-folder 470: 3)
    - Battard, Robert N. (Box-folder 470: 4)
    - Bechtel, Stephen D. (Box-folder 470: 5)
    - Beckmann, Petr (Box-folder 470: 6)
    - Black, Shirley Temple (Box-folder 470: 7)
    - Boas, Roger (Box-folder 470: 8)
    - Boeddeker, Alfred (Box-folder 470: 9)
    - Botha, Roelof F. (Box-folder 470: 10)
    - Bowen, Willliam Gordon (Box-folder 470: 11)
    - Branden, Nathaniel (Box-folder 470: 12)
    - Brodeur, Paul (Box-folder 470: 13)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box-folder 470: 14)
    - Brown, Ira (Box-folder 470: 15)
    - Buckley, James (Box-folder 470: 16)
    - Burger, Warren E. (Box-folder 470: 17)
    - Burke, Yvonne B. (Box-folder 470: 18)
    - Burton, Phillip (Box-folder 470: 19)
    - Carmichael, Gil (Box-folder 470: 20)
    - Chafetz, Morris (Box-folder 470: 21)
    - Charles, Prince of Wales (Box-folder 470: 22)
    - Clausen, A. W. (Box-folder 470: 23)
    - Clausen, Don (Box-folder 470: 24)
    - Colvin, Reynold (Box-folder 470: 25)
    - Courtright, Ham (Box-folder 470: 26)
    - Cousins, Norman (Box-folder 470: 27)
    - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 470: 28)
    - Davenport, Roy M. (Box-folder 470: 29)
    - Davis, Edward Chief (Box-folder 470: 30)
    - DeBolt, Dorothy (Box-folder 470: 31)
    - Dubs, Marne A. (Box-folder 470: 32)
    - Eckerd, Jack M. (Box-folder 471: 1)
    - Erdman, Paul (Box-folder 471: 2)
    - Ferris, Richard J. (Box-folder 471: 3)
    - Friedman, Milton (Box-folder 471: 4)
    - Friendly, Fred W. (Box-folder 471: 5)
    - Froehlke, Robert (Box-folder 471: 6)
    - Gain, Charles R. (Box-folder 471: 7)
    - Gilliam, Harold (Box-folder 471: 8)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 471: 9)
    - Greenspan, Alan (Box-folder 471: 10)
    - Haack, Robert W. (Box-folder 471: 11)
    - Halperin, Morton (Box-folder 471: 12)
    - Hamilton, Edward K. (Box-folder 471: 13)
    - Hanley, John W. (Box-folder 471: 14)
    - Hartley, Fred Lloyd (Box-folder 471: 15)
    - Hatch, Orrin (Box-folder 471: 16)
    - Hatfield, Robert S. (Box-folder 471: 17)
    - Hayakawa, Samuel I. (Box-folder 471: 18)
    - Hayward, Tom (Box-folder 471: 19)
    - Hemphill, Bernice (Box-folder 471: 20)
    - Hills, Roderick (Box-folder 471: 21)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 471: 22)
    - Hogness, David (Box-folder 471: 23)
    - Hussein, King of Jordan (Box-folder 472: 1)
    - Inauguration of officers, annual holiday concert (Box-folder 472: 2)
    - Inman, John Martin (Box-folder 472: 3)
    - Javits, Jacob (Box-folder 472: 4)
    - Kelley, Clarence (Box-folder 472: 5)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 472: 6)
    - Kolkowicz, Roman (Box-folder 472: 7)
    - Landers, Ann (Box-folder 472: 8)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 472: 9)
    - Lenczowski, George (Box-folder 472: 10)
    - Linowitz, Sol M. (Box-folder 472: 11)
    - McCaffrey, Stanley (Box-folder 472: 12)
    - McCloskey, Michael (Box-folder 472: 13)
    - Miki, Takeo (Box-folder 472: 14)
    - Muldoon, Robert D. (Box-folder 472: 15)
    - Nyerere, Julius (includes audiotape) (Box-folder 472: 16)
    - Pak, Tong-jin (Box-folder 472: 17)
    - Palme, Olof J. (Box-folder 472: 18)
    - Peacock, Andrew (Box-folder 472: 19)
    - Priolo, Paul (Box-folder 473: 1)
    - Rahman, Hasan (Box-folder 473: 2)
    - Ray, Dixy Lee (Box-folder 473: 3)
    - Rensch, Joseph (Box-folder 473: 4)
    - Rhodes, John J. (Box-folder 473: 5)
    - Riles, Wilson C. (Box-folder 473: 6)
    - Ruckelshaus, William D. (Box-folder 473: 7)
    - Salah, Abdullah Amin (Box-folder 473: 8)
    - Saud Al-Faisal ibn Abdul Aziz, Prince of Saudi Arabia (Box-folder 473: 9)
    - Saxbe, William B. (Box-folder 473: 10)
    - Schultze, Charles (Box-folder 473: 11)
    - Seawell, William T. (Box-folder 473: 12)
    - Shapiro, Martin (Box-folder 473: 13)
    - Silverman, Fred (Box-folder 473: 14)
    - Simon, William E. (Box-folder 473: 15)
    - Smith, Ian (Box-folder 473: 16)
    - Solzhenitsyn, Aleksandr (Box-folder 473: 17)
    - Staar, Richard F. (Box-folder 473: 18)
    - Togo, Fumihiko (Box-folder 473: 19)
    - Turner, Stansfield (Box-folder 474: 1)
    - Van Buren, Abigail (Box-folder 474: 2)
    - Walters, Barbara (Box-folder 474: 3)
    - Water panel (Box-folder 474: 4)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 474: 5)
    - Woods, Marion J. (Box-folder 474: 6)
    - Wurf, Jerry (Box-folder 474: 7)
    - Younger, Evelle J. (Box-folder 474: 8)
    - Zayyat, Mohammed Hassan (Box-folder 474: 9)
    - Zinchuk, Alexander (Box-folder 474: 10)
  - 1978
    - General. Speaker schedule for 1978 (Box-folder 474: 11)
    - Agee, William (Box-folder 474: 12)
    - Alioto, Robert (Box-folder 474: 13)
    - Anderson, Robert (Box-folder 474: 14)
    - Baker, Howard H. (Box-folder 474: 15)
    - Baldwin, Robert H. B. (Box-folder 474: 16)
    - Behr, Peter, and Howard Jarvis debate (Box-folder 474: 17)
    - Behr, Peter, and Howard Jarvis debate (Box-folder 475: 1)
    - Beran, Walter F. (Box-folder 475: 2)
    - Blumenthal, Michael W. (Box-folder 475: 3)
    - Boas, Roger (Box-folder 475: 4)
    - Borgstrom, Georg (Box-folder 475: 5)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box-folder 475: 6)
    - Brown, Harold (Box-folder 475: 7)
    - Browning, James, and Dan French (Box-folder 475: 8)
    - Burke, Yvonne Brathwaite (Box-folder 475: 9)
    - Butcher, Willard C. (Box-folder 475: 10)
    - Califano, Joseph (Box-folder 475: 11)
    - Carlucci, Frank C. (Box-folder 475: 12)
    - Case, Dwight (Box-folder 475: 13)
    - Castro, Fidel (Box-folder 475: 14)
    - Ceausescu, Nicolae (Box-folder 475: 15)
    - Clark, Ed (Box-folder 475: 16)
    - Clark, Ramsey (Box-folder 475: 17)
    - Cline, Ray (Box-folder 475: 18)
    - Comfort, Alexander (Box-folder 475: 19)
    - Crowther, Edward C. (Box-folder 475: 20)
    - Davidson, Basil (Box-folder 475: 21)
    - Desai, Morarji (Box-folder 475: 22)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 475: 23)
    - Drachkovitch, Milorad (Box-folder 475: 24)
    - Dubs, Marne A. (Box-folder 475: 25)
    - Duffy, James E. (Box-folder 476: 1)
    - Ellison, Gerald (Box-folder 476: 2)
    - Elton, Eunice (Box-folder 476: 3)
    - Energy issues speakers (Box-folder 476: 4)
    - Forbes, Malcolm (Box-folder 476: 5)
    - Frederick, Pauline (Box-folder 476: 6)
    - Freeman, David S. (Box-folder 476: 7)
    - Freivalds, John (Box-folder 476: 8)
    - Gann, Paul (Box-folder 476: 9)
    - Garamendi, John (Box-folder 476: 10)
    - Gardner, John (Box-folder 476: 11)
    - Goldberg, Arthur J. (Box-folder 476: 12)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 476: 13)
    - Goodlett, Carlton B. (Box-folder 476: 14)
    - Goody, Richard M. (Box-folder 476: 15)
    - Gould, William B. (Box-folder 476: 16)
    - Grayson, Jackson C. (Box-folder 476: 17)
    - Guarino, Philip A. (Box-folder 476: 18)
    - Haley, Alex (Box-folder 476: 19)
    - Hance, Margaret (Box-folder 476: 20)
    - Haris, Shearon (Box-folder 476: 22)
    - Harvey, Paul (Box-folder 476: 23)
    - Herringer, Frank (Box-folder 476: 24)
    - Herzog, Chaim (Box-folder 476: 25)
    - Hoadley, Walter E. (Box-folder 476: 26)
    - Holiday concert and installation of officers (Box-folder 476: 27)
    - Holman, Carl M. (Box-folder 477: 1)
    - Hooks, Benjamin L. (Box-folder 477: 2)
    - Hough, Gordon L. (Box-folder 477: 3)
    - Hussein, Saddam (Box-folder 477: 4)
    - Iloniemi, Jaakko (Box-folder 477: 5)
    - Jay, Peter (Box-folder 477: 6)
    - Johnson, Huey D. (Box-folder 477: 7)
    - Jordan, Vernon E. (Box-folder 477: 8)
    - Kahn, Alfred E. (Box-folder 477: 9)
    - Kahn, Herman (Box-folder 477: 10)
    - Kates, Don B. (Box-folder 477: 11)
    - Kennedy, Edward M. (Box-folder 477: 12)
    - Kim, Yong Shik (Box-folder 477: 13)
    - Kimball, Charles N. (Box-folder 477: 14)
    - Krikorian, Robert V. (Box-folder 477: 15)
    - Laboulaye, Fran?ois de (Box-folder 477: 17)
    - Laird, Melvin (Box-folder 477: 18)
    - Lévesque, René (Box-folder 477: 19)
    - Lin, Paul T. K. (Box-folder 477: 20)
    - Love, Ruth (Box-folder 477: 21)
    - Lovell, James A. (Box-folder 477: 22)
    - McCarthy, Leo (Box-folder 477: 23)
    - McIntyre, James T. (Box-folder 477: 24)
    - McLeod, John T., and Webb Maddux (Box-folder 477: 25)
    - MacNaughton, Malcolm (Box-folder 478: 1)
    - Mankiewicz, Frank (Box-folder 478: 2)
    - Marcos, Ferdinand (Box-folder 478: 3)
    - Marel, Sayed (Box-folder 478: 4)
    - Marriott, John W., Jr. (Box-folder 478: 5)
    - Martinez de Hoz, José Alfredo (Box-folder 478: 6)
    - May, Michael M. (Box-folder 478: 7)
    - Maytag, L. B. (Box-folder 478: 8)
    - Meyers, Gerald C. (Box-folder 478: 9)
    - Miller, Len (Box-folder 478: 10)
    - Moscone, George (Box-folder 478: 11)
    - Mueller, George E. (Box-folder 478: 12)
    - Nader, Ralph (Box-folder 478: 13)
    - National opinion poll (3 possible speakers) (Box-folder 478: 14)
    - O'Kennedy, Michael (Box-folder 478: 15)
    - Olivarez, Graciela (Box-folder 478: 16)
    - Oreffice, Paul F. (Box-folder 478: 17)
    - Peres, Shimon (Box-folder 478: 18)
    - Pieper, Oscar (Box-folder 478: 19)
    - Pinson, William M. (Box-folder 478: 20)
    - Poe, Bryce (Box-folder 478: 21)
    - Quinn, John R. (Box-folder 478: 22)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 478: 23)
    - Roberts, Denys (Box-folder 478: 24)
    - Romney, George (Box-folder 478: 25)
    - Ryrie, William (Box-folder 478: 26)
    - Safdie, Irwin J. (Box-folder 478: 27)
    - Scammon, Richard M. (Box-folder 478: 28)
    - Schlafly, Phyllis Stewart (Box-folder 478: 29)
    - Siebert, Muriel (Box-folder 478: 30)
    - Singlaub, John K. (Box-folder 479: 1)
    - Sloss, Richard (Box-folder 479: 2)
    - Smart, Edwin (Box-folder 479: 3)
    - Smith, Ian (Box-folder 479: 4)
    - Stang, Alan (Box-folder 479: 5)
    - Starr, Chauncey (Box-folder 479: 6)
    - Stetson, John C. (Box-folder 479: 7)
    - Stilwell, Richard G. (Box-folder 479: 8)
    - Strauss, Robert S. (Box-folder 479: 9)
    - Suzman, Helen (Box-folder 479: 10)
    - Togni, Alberto (Box-folder 479: 11)
    - Togo, Fumihiko (Box-folder 479: 12)
    - Troyanovsky, Olyeg (Box-folder 479: 13)
    - Van de Kemp, John (Box-folder 479: 14)
    - Wahed, Joseph A. (Box-folder 479: 15)
    - Warda, Samuel S. (Box-folder 479: 16)
    - Watson, Clarke (Box-folder 479: 17)
    - Weicker, Lowell P. (Box-folder 479: 18)
    - Wilcox, Thomas (Box-folder 479: 19)
    - Williams, A. Cecil (Box-folder 479: 20)
    - Wilson, Peter (Box-folder 479: 21)
    - Wilson, Robert C. (Box-folder 479: 22)
    - Wirt, Robert (Box-folder 479: 23)
    - Witkin, Bernard E. (Box-folder 479: 24)
    - Witt, John W. (Box-folder 479: 25)
    - Younger, Evelle J. (Box-folder 480: 1)
  - 1979
    - General (Box-folder 480: 2)
    - Agnew, H. M. (Box-folder 480: 3)
    - Annual holiday concert (Box-folder 480: 4)
    - Baudouin I, King of the Belgians (Box-folder 480: 5)
    - Berg, A. Scott (Box-folder 480: 6)
    - Bergland, Bob S. (Box-folder 480: 7)
    - Bernstein, Leonard (Box-folder 480: 8)
    - Biaggini, Benjamin (Box-folder 480: 9)
    - Blasdell, Clark (Box-folder 480: 10)
    - Blum, Yehuda (Box-folder 480: 11)
    - Blumenthal, W. Michael (Box-folder 480: 12)
    - Bolt, Bruce A. (Box-folder 480: 13)
    - Bond, Langhorne (Box-folder 480: 14)
    - Boorstin, Daniel J. (Box-folder 480: 15)
    - Brain, Donald (Box-folder 480: 16)
    - Brill, Steve (Box-folder 480: 17)
    - Brown, Harold (Box-folder 480: 18)
    - Brown, Sam (Box-folder 480: 19)
    - Bryne, Jane (Box-folder 480: 20)
    - Business Week panel of editors (Box-folder 480: 21)
    - Califano, Joseph (Box-folder 480: 22)
    - Campbell, Alan K. (Box-folder 480: 23)
    - Campbell, William (Box-folder 480: 24)
    - Carey, Hugh (Box-folder 480: 25)
    - Castillo, Leonel J. (Box-folder 481: 1)
    - Cedronio, Paolo Pansa (Box-folder 481: 2)
    - Celeste, Richard (Box-folder 481: 3)
    - Clark, C. Joseph (Box-folder 481: 4)
    - Cline, Ray (Box-folder 481: 5)
    - Clinton, Bill (Box-folder 481: 6)
    - Cockran, Thad (Box-folder 481: 7)
    - Cohen, A. Jerome (Box-folder 481: 8)
    - Collins, Brien (Box-folder 481: 9)
    - Connor, Joseph E. (Box-folder 481: 10)
    - Cooke, Alistair (Box-folder 481: 11)
    - Cranston, Alan (Box-folder 481: 12)
    - Curb, Mike (Box-folder 481: 13)
    - Cults (overview speaker) (Box-folder 481: 14)